Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
6047
Kheel Center
109 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into five sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Boxes 44-45 and 102-109 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6047: Archives Information File
6047: Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
6047: Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
6047: Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
6047: Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Boxes 44-45 and 102-109 have not been inventoried at this time.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 89, Folder: 1 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Benefits and Family Finances, 1958; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Author: New York Department of Labor
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Box: 89, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Reserves, 1933; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Author: Robert F. Wagner
    Notes: June 12, 1933
- Box: 89, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Dyna-Soar Contract Cancellation, 1965; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Author: U.S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency
    Notes: July 1965
- Box: 89, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employment and Material Position of Temporarily Unemployed Workers, 1965; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Author: Yugoslav Experiences
- Box: 89, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Les Syndicats Americains, Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Author: Les Editions Syndicalistes
    Language: French.
  - Item 2: The Duty to Bargain, 1960; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Author: American Newspaper Publishers Association
    Notes: October 27, 1960
  - Item 3: Proposed Federal Rules of Evidence, Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Author: Kellwood Company
  - Item 4: How to Avoid Unfair Labor Practices, 1945; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Author: Labor Relations Institute
- Box: 89, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Relocation: How to Avoid Labor Woes, 1961; Publication (Box 89, Folder 6)
    Author: Industrial Relations News
    Notes: July 1961
  - Item 2: What Management Can Say During a Union Campaign, 1962; Publication (Box 89, Folder 6)
    Author: Hugh P. Husband
    Notes: September 1962
- Box: 89, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Series Studies in Social and Economic Sciences, Publication (Box 89, Folder 7)
    Author: George Washington University
- Box: 89, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Union Security, Publication (Box 89, Folder 8)
    Author: Orme W. Phelps
  - Item 2: The Case for the Union Shop, Publication (Box 89, Folder 8)
    Author: Industrial Union Department
  - Item 3: Union Security, Publication (Box 89, Folder 8)
    Author: Workers' Educational Association
  - Item 4: "14-B," Freedom, Free Agency, and "Union Security", Publication (Box 89, Folder 8)
    Author: Vernon H. Jensen
- Box: 89, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Why Journalists Favor Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 89, Folder 9)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce of the United States
- Box: 89, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Citizen and the United Nations, Publication (Box 89, Folder 10)
    Author: League of Women Voters
  - Item 2: Transition from League of Nations to United Nations, Publication (Box 89, Folder 10)
    Author: Henry Reiff
- Box: 89, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Career Indications Among Junior Officers, 1969; Publication (Box 89, Folder 11)
    Author: Faye Shenk
    Notes: September 1969
  - Item 2: Field Test of the Weighted Airman Promotion System, 1969; Publication (Box 89, Folder 11)
    Author: Janos B. Koplyay
    Notes: May 1969
- Box: 89, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Walter Hill Scott: Pioneer in Personnel Management, Publication (Box 89, Folder 12)
    Author: Edmund C. Lynch
  - Item 2: Extension of the Weighted Airman Promotion System to Grades E-8 and E-9, 1970; Publication (Box 89, Folder 12)
    Notes: January 1970
  - Item 3: Equivalence of Afoot Scores for Different Educational Levels, 1969; Publication (Box 89, Folder 12)
    Author: Ernest C. Tupes, Robert E. Miller
- Box: 89, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Facts About Taxes and Public Spending, Publication (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Projecting Federal Revenues and Expenditures, Publication (Box 89, Folder 13)
    Author: Gerhard Colm & Peter Wagner
  - Item 3: Federal Expenditure and Tax Policies, 1946; Publication (Box 89, Folder 13)
    Notes: December 1946
  - Item 4: The Stabilizing Budget Policy, Publication (Box 89, Folder 13)
    Author: Committee for Economic Development
  - Item 5: Taxing to Spend, 1949; Publication (Box 89, Folder 13)
    Notes: March 1949
  - Item 6: Looking Toward a Balanced Budget, 1946; Publication (Box 89, Folder 13)
    Notes: November 1946
  - Item 7: Preparing for the 1949 Federal Budget, 1947; Publication (Box 89, Folder 13)
    Notes: October 1947
- Box: 89, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Directions, 1968; Publication (Box 89, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. Defense Supply Agency
- Box: 89, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Manpower, 1941; Publication (Box 89, Folder 15)
    Author: Leo M. Cherne, Hugh M. Cole
    Notes: December 21, 1941
- Box: 89, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Summary of Simpo-I Model Development, 1969; Publication (Box 89, Folder 16)
    Author: U.S. Army
    Notes: March 1969
- Box: 89, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Biographical Sources for the United States, Publication (Box 89, Folder 17)
    Author: The Library of Congress
- Box: 89, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Your 1970 Census, 1969; Publication (Box 89, Folder 18)
    Author: Maxwell S. Stewart
    Notes: February 1969
  - Item 2: Census Tract Manual, 1966; Publication (Box 89, Folder 18)
    Author: U.S. Department of Commerce
    Notes: January 1966
  - Item 3: The Census of Population and Housing, 1970; Publication (Box 89, Folder 18)
- Box: 89, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: How to Improve Administration of the Federal Employees' Compensation Benefits Program, 1975; Publication (Box 89, Folder 19)
    Author: U.S. General Accounting Office
    Notes: March 13, 1975
- Box: 89, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Two Years of Emergency Conservation Work, 1935; Publication (Box 89, Folder 20)
    Author: Civilian Conservation Corps
    Notes: March 31, 1935
- Box: 89, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Diversion of Exports through Canada, 1971; Publication (Box 89, Folder 21)
    Author: John R. Immer
- Box: 89, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Copy, 1962; Publication (Box 89, Folder 22)
    Author: U.S. President's Advisory Committee on Labor-Management Policy
    Notes: October 4, 1962
- Box: 89, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights Commission, 1972; Publication (Box 89, Folder 23)
    Author: U.S. Committee on the Judiciary
    Notes: February 24, 1972
- Box: 89, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Legislation Affecting Certain Members' Retirement, 1971; Publication (Box 89, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Post Office and Civil Service
    Notes: July 28, 1971
- Box: 89, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: An Unconstitutional Roadblock to Democratic Legislation, Publication (Box 89, Folder 25)
    Author: CIO
- Box: 89, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Supreme Court and the Constitution, 1936; Publication (Box 89, Folder 26)
    Author: Public Affairs Pamphlets
  - Item 2: What's Happening to Our Constitution?, 1946; Publication (Box 89, Folder 26)
    Author: Robert E. Cushman
- Box: 89, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The National Peril, Publication (Box 89, Folder 27)
    Author: Franklin A. Lindsay
- Box: 89, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Use of Contractor Personnel in the Department of Defense, 1965; Publication (Box 89, Folder 28)
    Notes: July 13, 1965
  - Item 2: Use of Contractor Personnel in Department of Defense, 1965; Publication (Box 89, Folder 28)
    Author: U.S. Congress
    Notes: March 2, 1965
- Box: 89, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Program Assistance and Services to States and Local Governments, 1971; Publication (Box 89, Folder 29)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor
    Notes: September 1971
- Box: 89, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Manpower Development and Training Activities, 1967; Publication (Box 89, Folder 30)
    Notes: November 8, 1967
  - Item 2: Supplemental Appropriation for the Department of Labor, 1971; Publication (Box 89, Folder 30)
    Author: U.S. Senate
  - Item 3: Supplemental Appropriation for the Department of Labor, 1972; Publication (Box 89, Folder 30)
- Box: 89, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Employment Opportunities in the Bureau of Sport Fisheries & Wildlife, Publication (Box 89, Folder 31)
    Author: U.S. Department of the Interior
- Box: 89, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Projections for the Seventies, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
    Author: United Community Funds and Councils of America
  - Item 2: The Labor Market and Potential Output of the Federal Reserve-MIT Econometric Model, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
    Author: A.J. Tella, P.A. Tinsley
  - Item 3: Economics for the 1960's, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
    Author: First National Bank of Hawaii
  - Item 4: Looking Forward: the Abundant Society, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
    Author: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
  - Item 5: Highlights of the 1968 Manpower Report of the President, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: The Pulse Beat of Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
    Author: McGraw- Hill
    Notes: June 1946
  - Item 7: The Way America Works, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - Item 8: The Miracle of America, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
    Author: The Advertising Council
  - Item 9: The Emerging Economic Problems of the 1960's, Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
    Author: National Association of Manufacturers
    Notes: January 1960
  - Item 10: Trade Union Delegation's Study Trip in the United States, 1949; Publication (Box 89, Folder 32)
    Author: Arbeidernes Faglige Landsorganisasjon
- Box: 89, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Military and Economic Demobilization of the United States, 1943; Publication (Box 89, Folder 33)
    Author: National Resources Planning Board
    Notes: June 1943
  - Item 2: Poverty and Deprivation in the U.S., Publication (Box 89, Folder 33)
    Author: Conference on Economic Progress
  - Item 3: Economic Base Survey of the Potomac River Service Area, Publication (Box 89, Folder 33)
- Box: 89, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Recession, Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Problems of the American Economy, 1961; Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Author: Paul A. Samuelson
  - Item 3: Economic Crisis in the United States, Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Author: Scott Nearing
  - Item 4: Business Outlook, 1962; Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Author: The Conference Board
  - Item 5: Assessing the Economic Scene, Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Item 6: U.S. Economic Growth, 1966; Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Author: Joint Economic Committee
  - Item 7: Reducing Tax Rates for Production and Growth, 1962; Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Notes: December 1962
  - Item 8: Perspective on 1960, Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Author: Federal Reserve Bank of New York
  - Item 9: A People's Program for Jobs and Security, Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Author: Communist Party
  - Item 10: The Emerging Economic Problems of the 1960's, Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Item 11: The Federal Government's Program of Economic Growth Studies, 1965; Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Author: Jack Alterman
    Notes: April 23, 1965
  - Item 12: The Potential Economic Growth in the United States, 1960; Publication (Box 89, Folder 34)
    Author: U.S. Joint Economic Committee
    Notes: January 30, 1960
- Box: 89, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The Economy, 1970; Publication (Box 89, Folder 35)
- Box: 89, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 89, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Report on Economic Statistics, 1956; Publication (Box 89, Folder 36)
    Notes: January 5, 1956
- Box: 89, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Position of Business on Fiscal and Wage Policy in Depression, 1949; Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: National Planning Association
    Notes: August 30, 1949
  - Item 2: What Foreign Trade Means to You, 1946; Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Fiscal and Monetary Policy for High Employment, Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Item 4: Toward Economic Security, 1935; Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: President's Committee on Economic Security
  - Item 5: Present Crisis of Labor and Industry, Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: S. Stanwood Menken
  - Item 6: Toward More Production, Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Item 7: The People's Plan for Reconversion, Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: The American Labor Party
  - Item 8: In What Direction is America Moving?, 1946; Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: Eduard C. Lindeman
    Notes: June 15, 1946
  - Item 9: Business Management and Economic Analysis, 1947; Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Item 10: Why We Make Our Living the Way We Do, Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: Syracuse University
  - Item 11: A Summary View of American Economic Policies, 1943; Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: Sumner H. Slichter, Robert D. Calkins, J. Franklin Ebersole
    Notes: May 13, 1943
  - Item 12: Eliminating Economic Warfare, Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: University of Denver
  - Item 13: Management's Responsibility to Capitalism, Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Item 14: Victory for Freedom, 1944; Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Notes: December 1944
  - Item 15: The Fallacies and Dangers of the Townsend Plan, 1936; Publication (Box 89, Folder 37)
    Author: Walter E. Spahr
    Notes: January 3, 1936
- Box: 89, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 89, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: From Guide Posts to Guidelines to ?, Publication (Box 89, Folder 38)
    Author: Machinery and Allied Products Institute
  - Item 2: An Analysis of Professor Arthur F. Burns' Critique of the Council's Position, 1961; Publication (Box 89, Folder 38)
    Author: Council of Economic Advisers
    Notes: June 10, 1961
- Box: 89, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The Economy Under Law, Publication (Box 89, Folder 39)
    Author: W.H. Ferry
  - Item 2: Fiscal and Monetary Policy for High Employment, Publication (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: Economic Topics, Publication (Box 89, Folder 39)
    Author: Joint Council on Economic Education
  - Item 4: Guidelines, Informal Controls, and the Market Place, Publication (Box 89, Folder 39)
    Author: George P. Shultz, Robert Z. Aliber
- Box: 89, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 89, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Maintaining Stability at High Employment, Publication (Box 89, Folder 40)
    Author: Georgetown University
  - Item 2: Management in an Era of Dynamic Technology, 1959; Publication (Box 89, Folder 40)
    Author: Massachusetts Institute of Technology
  - Item 3: Incentives for Economic Growth, 1961; Publication (Box 89, Folder 40)
    Author: Opinion Research Corporation
- Box: 89, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 89, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Promise of Economic Growth, Publication (Box 89, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: The Promise of Economic Growth, Publication (Box 89, Folder 41)
  - Item 3: Regaining Balance in a High Employment Economy, Publication (Box 89, Folder 41)
    Author: Henry W. Briefs
  - Item 4: Survey of Economic Models for Analysis of Disarmament Impacts, 1965; Publication (Box 89, Folder 41)
    Author: Daniel B. Suits
- Box: 89, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 89, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: The Federal Budget, Inflation, and Full Employment, 1969; Publication (Box 89, Folder 42)
    Notes: November 1969
- Box: 90, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Managing a Full Employment Economy, Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Freedom is Our Responsibility, Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Author: E.H. Fallon
- Box: 90, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Prospects for the American Economy During the Post-Vietnam Period, 1967; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Author: Murray L. Weidenbaum
    Notes: July 1967
- Box: 90, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor's Role in Building a Better Society, Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Author: I.W. Abel
  - Item 2: Policies for American Economic Progress in the Seventies, 1970; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Author: President's Task Force on Economic Growth
    Notes: May 1970
- Box: 90, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: International Migration of Intellectual Talent, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Author: American Council on Education
    Notes: November 17, 1966
  - Item 2: Immigration and the Changing Economy, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Author: Frank L. Mott
    Notes: July 18, 1966
  - Item 3: The Interagency Council and the "Brain Drain" in Developing Countries, 1967; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. Department of State
    Notes: October 6, 1967
  - Item 4: U.S. Immigration Policy and World Population Problems, Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Author: Virgil Salera
  - Item 5: The Stranger at Our Gate, Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Author: Hubert H. Humphrey
  - Item 6: What Shall We Do About Immigration?, Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Author: Maurice R. Davie
  - Item 7: The Uprooted, Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Author: American R.D.M. Corporation
  - Item 8: Authorizing Additional Immigrants into the United States, 1952; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. House of Representatives
    Notes: March 24, 1952
  - Item 9: Scientific Brain Drain from the Developing Countries, 1968; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 28, 1968
- Box: 90, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Comments on Selective Features of Proposed Legislation on the Public Employment Service, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Author: Leonard P. Adams
    Notes: March 24, 1966
- Box: 90, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Organization of Federal Executive Departments and Agencies, 1955; Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 1, 1955
  - Item 2: Improving Service to the Public, 1967; Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
    Author: U.S. Civil Service Commission
    Notes: June 1967
  - Item 3: Uneconomical Use of Federal Funds, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Box: 90, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights Responsibilities of the Federal Power Commission, 1972; Publication (Box 90, Folder 7)
    Notes: September 1972
- Box: 90, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Midwest Conference on Foreign Economic Policy, 1962; Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
    Notes: October 16, 1962
  - Item 2: Agricultural Surpluses and Export Policy, Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
    Author: Raymond F. Mikesell
  - Item 3: The Impact of U.S. Foreign Economic Policy on the War on Poverty, Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
    Author: Trade Relations Council
  - Item 4: International Trade and Investment in the 70's, Publication (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Box: 90, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: An Indissoluble Friendship, 1929; Publication (Box 90, Folder 9)
    Author: E.H.H. Simmons
    Notes: February 22, 1929
- Box: 90, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Committee Publications and Policies Governing their Distribution, 1966; Publication (Box 90, Folder 10)
    Notes: February 20, 1966
- Box: 90, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Report of the Industrial Commission, Publication (Box 90, Folder 11)
    Author: Richard T. Ely
- Box: 90, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Economic Fact and Fantasy, 1967; Publication (Box 90, Folder 12)
    Author: G.C. Allen
  - Item 2: Pioneers of American Industry, Publication (Box 90, Folder 12)
    Author: News Front
- Box: 90, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Principles and Procedures for the Review and Maintenance of the Establishment Standard Industrial Classification Manual, 1968; Publication (Box 90, Folder 13)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of the Budget
- Box: 90, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Sources of State Information and State Industrial Directories, Publication (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Box: 90, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Manufacturing Industries, Publication (Box 90, Folder 15)
    Author: Century Press
- Box: 90, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Garfieldized, 1918; Publication (Box 90, Folder 16)
    Author: Industrial Economist
    Notes: January 25, 1918
  - Item 2: What Have You Given?, 1918; Publication (Box 90, Folder 16)
    Notes: April 10, 1918
  - Item 3: A Time for Sane Thought and Good Citizenship, 1918; Publication (Box 90, Folder 16)
    Notes: June 25, 1918
  - Item 4: The Time Has Come, 1918; Publication (Box 90, Folder 16)
    Notes: July 10, 1918
  - Item 5: Reaping the Whirlwind, 1917; Publication (Box 90, Folder 16)
    Notes: October 25, 1917
  - Item 6: This Law Prohibits Strikes, 1917; Publication (Box 90, Folder 16)
    Notes: August 10, 1917
- Box: 90, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Industrial Production Indexes, 1965; Publication (Box 90, Folder 17)
    Author: U.S. Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve System
    Notes: September 1965
- Box: 90, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Effectiveness and Administration of the Kilmer Corps Center for Men, 1969; Publication (Box 90, Folder 18)
    Notes: September 19, 1969
  - Item 2: Review of Establishment and Operation of St. Petersburg Job Corps Center for Women, 1968; Publication (Box 90, Folder 18)
    Notes: February 5, 1968
  - Item 3: Effectiveness and Administration of the Albuquerue Job Corps Center for Women, 1969; Publication (Box 90, Folder 18)
    Notes: July 24, 1969
- Box: 90, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Appalachian Regional Development Act, 1967; Publication (Box 90, Folder 19)
    Notes: January 23, 1967
- Box: 90, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Pathway to Employment, Publication (Box 90, Folder 20)
- Box: 90, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 90, Folder 21)